

RIO SETIAWAN

riosetiawan1997@gmail.com | +6285891217032 | Jakarta Timur, Jakarta, Indonesia 13450 | https://riosetiawan97.github.io/portfolio/

Summary

Graduated from Bina Nusantara University, with almost 5 years of experience as a Software Engineer.

I have 2 year of experience as a web developer using .Net and I also have 3 years of experience developing desktop-based applications using Magic. Currently searching for a .NET application development position to utilize my skills and take the next step in my career, which is to actively contribute to the overall success of any business I work for.

Education

- Bachelor degree Computer Science, Bina Nusantara University, Jakarta (Aug 2021 Aug 2023). GPA
 3.56.
- Associate Degree Informatics Management, Gunadarma University, Jakarta (Aug 2015 Aug 2018).
 GPA 3.71.

Work Experiences

PT. Indocyber Global Teknologi (Apr 2019 - Okt 2022)

Magic Developer

At PT Indocyber Global Teknologi, I developed mobile and desktop-based recruitment applications for use in internal companies using Magic XPA 3.3 and MySql database.

At PT Indocyber Global Teknologi I was also placed in several client companies as follows:

PT. Astra Credit Company (Aug 2019 - Feb 2020)

Magic Developer

- Developed a desktop-based customer data input application using Magic Unipass and Oracle database.
- Conduct application testing with the Quality Control team.
- Discuss with System Analyst team regarding application development.

PT. Astra OtoParts (Mar 2020 - Apr 2022)

Magic Developer

- Perform maintenance on the ERP application at the Business Unit of PT Astra OtoParts.
- Create program documentation.
- Make application changes according to user requests.
- Perform System Integration Testing and User Acceptance Test.
- Support Go-Live.
- Perform Operational Support for ERP applications.

PT. Infinite Creative Teknologi (Oct 2022 – Jan 2024)

.Net Developer

- Developed Web-based applications using .Net Core, ASP.Net and .Net MVC, SQL Server database.
- Coordinate with System Analyst, related to the application that will be developed.
- Perform System Integration Testing with the Quality Control Team.

PT. Kamoro Maxima Integra (Jan 2024 - Present)

Software Engineer

At PT. Kamoro Maxima Integra I was placed at the client company PT. Tower Bersama Group.

PT. Tower Bersama Group (Jan 2024 - Present)

Software Engineer

- Developed Web-based applications using .Net Core, ASP.Net and .Net MVC, SQL Server database.
- Coordinate with Product Manager, related to the application that will be developed.
- Perform System Integration Testing, User Acceptance Test and Support Go-Live.

Projects

Customer Registration Application (Aug 2019 – Feb 2020)

Magic Developer

Developed a desktop-based Customer data input application by using Magic Unipass and Oracle database. with this application, users can input customer data into the database.

Migration and Operational ERP (Mar 2020 – Apr 2022)

Magic Developer

Migrate erp applications from magic 8 technology to magic XPA, and perform operational support, for applications that have been developed.

Recruitment Aplication (May 2022 – Oct 2022)

Magic Developer

Developed a desktop-based recruitment application using Magic XPA and SQL Server database. With this application, users can manage the resource needs of clients, such as recruiting new employees.

Purchasing Application (Oct 2022 – Jan 2024)

.Net Developer

Develop a purchasing application that can be used for retail stores. with this application users can order the goods needed to the central factory.

"Continuous Improvement" Application (Jan 2024 – Apr 2024)

.Net Developer

Developing a web-based application, which can be used by Tower Bersama Group employees to register their ideas that can be implemented in the work environment.

Office Assistant Application (Apr 2024 – Jul 2024)

.Net Developer

Developing a web-based application, which can be used by General Affairs Division employees to monitor the work carried out by Office Boys every day.

Vendor Contract Application (Jul 2024 – Present)

.Net Developer

Developing a web-based application, which can be used by Vendor Management Division employees to make it easier to manage Tower Bersama Group vendor contract documents.

Key Skills and Expertise

- •.Net Core, PHP C#, ASP.NET, .Net MVC, Magic XPA, JQuery, Javascript, Ajax, HTML, CSS.
- Ms. SQL Server, Oracle, My SQL, Query, Stored Procedure, Function, View, SQL Job, Microsoft SQL Server Integration Services.
- SQL Server Management Studio, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, Git, Github.
- SQL Server (2008, 2017), IIS 7, IIS 8, Visual Studio 2022, Windows Server (2012, 2016), Telerik Kendo UI.
- Five years' experience as software developer.

Certification

- Fundamental DBMS (Gunadarma University)
- Fundamental ERP (Gunadarma University)
- XML Programming Language (Gunadarma University)
- Microsoft Dynamic Nav For Beginner (Gunadarma University)
- Oracle For Beginner (Gunadarma University)
- Java For Intermediate (Gunadarma University)
- Oracle For Intermediate (Gunadarma University)

Languages

- Indonesian
- English (Passive)